{
    "subject": "resource/John_and_Mary_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_directed_by_Peter_Yates",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film 'John and Mary' is Films directed by Peter Yates.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9258253574371338,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film 'John and Mary'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9100325107574463,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'John and Mary'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8021594285964966,
            "question": "What are some other films directed by Peter Yates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712475597858429,
            "question": "Is Peter Yates a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6628396511077881,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'John and Mary'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6305129528045654,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'John and Mary' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6099199056625366,
            "question": "When was the film 'John and Mary' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4141567647457123,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for their roles in 'John and Mary'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28965187072753906,
            "question": "Did 'John and Mary' receive critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23213037848472595,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'John and Mary'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film 'John and Mary' is Films directed by Peter Yates.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6973_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did 'John and Mary' receive critical acclaim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6973_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors known for their roles in 'John and Mary'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6973_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'John and Mary' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6973_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6973_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about films directed by Peter Yates, including \"John and Mary,\" which confirms that the subject of the film \"John and Mary\" is indeed related to films directed by Peter Yates."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}